北邮人；信通院单身男博士；四月一日君  制作（纯属交流用）
学术交流、节操一地、介绍对象请 Email： 317919568@qq.com
如果我能够把他放到你面前会怎么样？
What if I could put him in front of you?
那个毁了你一生的男人?
The man that ruined your life?
如果我能够向你保证你最好逃离他
If I could guarantee that you'd get away with it
你会杀了他么？
would you kill him?
（左贴纸）永远不要做明天需要完成的事情
（右贴纸）如果你成功了，永远不要再次去尝试
布莱克默十字勋章
The Blackmore Cross.
我明白这是你的第二次得此殊荣
I understand it's your second.
祝贺你！
Congratulations.
你光荣的得到了它
You have served honorably.
那就这些了？
So that's it?
董事会的指令会很快到来
The order from the board will come through shortly.
是最终的命令么？
The final order?
是的
Yes.
那个放置炸弹的人呢？
And the Bomber?
这已经不再是你需要考虑的问题了
It's not your problem anymore.
我想我不需要提醒你
I don't need to remind you
你最终任务的重要性
of the critical nature of your final mission.
那么请你先休息吧
So please rest.
每个嫌疑犯告诫我们
Every suspect educates us.
让我们所作所为变得更好
Makes us better at what we do.
只有这些反社会的人
No more than this elusive sociopath.
才是高效的
He's efficient.
他能够精准的掌控时间
Precise with his timings.
媒体将其成为闪灭爆炸人
The press have dubbed him the Fizzle Bomber.
我们这次阻止了他
We stopped him this time.
但这次只是一次小规模袭击
But this was only a small attack.
这才是他的宏伟计划
This is his grand plan.
1975年3月
March 1975.
这一天他不断改变
He keeps changing the day.
爆炸幅度波及10个纽约街区
The explosion will level 10 blocks of New York
并导致11000人死亡
and leave over 11,000 dead.
我们所做的阻止他的一切已经失败了
Everything we've done to stop him has failed.
但这次我很接近了
But I was close this time.
仅仅再试一次
Just one more try.
移植手术已经完成
Grafts have taken.
再造移植很稳定
The reconstructive transplant is stable.
但是你必须明白
But you understand
你将会看上去与你以前不一样了
you will look different to what you remember.
眼睛将会治愈
Eyes will heal.
为了这次终极任务，你需要很好地恢复
You should recover well for this final mission.
接着我将会退役
And then I'll be decommissioned.
这不是仅仅身体的伤害
It's not just the physical injuries.
你已经积累了相当多的战斗经验
You've logged more field hours
这些经验超过了我之前安排的所有特工
than any of the other agents I've been assigned to.
这个任务是真实的
The risks are real.
疤痕已经开始很好地复合了
The scars have begun to heal nicely.
你坏掉的声带已经恢复
Your vocal cord damage has reduced
但是也不是原来的那种声音
but will not regrow exactly the same way.
我的歌（站）唱（斗）事（任）业（务）开始了
There goes my singing career.
这需要一段时间适应
It will take some getting used to.
我改变了很多
I've changed so much
我怀疑我老妈是否都能认出我
that I doubt my own mother would recognize me.
任务指示今天将会到达
The order finally came through today.
我想
I guess
这是不可避免的了
it was inevitable.
等到你听到这个的时候，七年过去了
By the time you listen to this seven years will have passed.
我们的第一个任务
Our first mission
也会像我们最后一个（任务）一样重要
is just as important as our last.
每个任务都会使得我们更加接近终极任务
Each one getting us closer to our final destination.
先生，请举起你的右手
Sir, please raise your right hand.
你会庄严地的发誓去遵守
Do you solemnly swear to uphold the rules and regulations
-代号7286以后的规则和条款么？
-是的
- set forth by T.B.R. Code 7286?
- I do.
你会接受任何任务条款，而这些条款
Do you accept that any diversion from your mission parameters
将会导致你立即上军事法庭，定罪
will result in immediate court martial?
And if convicted
或判注射死刑么？
death by lethal injection.
我接受
I do.
谢谢，先生
Thank you, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
时间，赶上了我们所有的人
Time. It catches up with us all.
即使那些在我们行当里的人
Even those in our line of work.
我想你可能会说我们天赋秉异
I guess you could say we're gifted.
上帝啊，这听起来是多么傲慢
God, Jesus, it sounds arrogant saying that out loud.
好吧
All right.
我将以一个更好的方式来说
I'll put it a better way.
我想你可能会说
I guess you could say
我们与生俱来就是干这行的
we were born into this job.
影片名：前目的地/宿命论
（翻译：四月一日君，PS：头一次翻译，天马行空或无节操之处请多多吐槽
QQ：317919568）
嘿，看看这个怪人
Hey, look at this freak.
这边请，Derek
There you go, Derek.
我能帮你什么吗？
What can I get you?
老恩酒
Old Underwear.
老恩酒。不加冰？
Old Underwear. Straight up?
留下这瓶
Leave the bottle.
从你表情上，我猜你不是在庆祝
From the look of you
I'm guessing you're not celebrating.
从我的样子？
From the look of me?
我看上去像什么？
What do I look like?
上帝，仅仅是套话而已
Just making conversation. Jesus.
他倒下了
He's down!
嘿，兄弟，再来两扎（好爽啊）
Hey, bud, two more.
巡洋舰（饮烈酒后喝的饮料），对吗？
Chaser, right?
你是新来的
You're new.
是的，我来这里工作才几周
Yeah, I've been working here a couple of weeks.
是吗？工作感觉如何？
Yeah? How's it working out?
相当乏味
It's been quiet.
人们都待在家里
People staying home.
因为那个可恶的闪灭炸弹人吗？
Because of the big, bad Fizzle Bomber?
是的，我想
Yeah, I guess.
我却很喜欢
Love it.
喜欢躲藏使得你更加安全
Like hiding makes you any safer.
你不害怕吗？
Doesn't scare you?
害怕地铁里面每一个怪人是无济于事的
Worrying about every freak show on the subway won't change things.
这倒是
That is true.
我在附近从没见过你
Haven't seen you around.
你经常来这？
You come here often?
你是谁啊，是搞基的吗？
What are you, a faggot?
你啥意思？
What's your problem?
嘿！
Hey!
上帝，我只是逗你玩呢
I was joking man. Jesus.
恩~好吧，但是那一点不逗比
Yeah, well, that's not funny.
告诉我一个好的
Tell me a good one then.
-啥，一个笑话？
-是的，来吧
- What, a joke?
- Yeah, come on.
你懂的，免费来一撸，来吧
You know, a free shot. Come on.
不，不，我啥也不知道
No, no, I don't know any.
不看僧面看佛面，你在酒吧工作肯定听过笑话
You work in a bar for Chrissakes. Surely you know a joke.
不，我不爱讲笑话，从不记这些
No, I'm terrible with jokes. Never remember them.
来一个？
One joke?
好吧，我知道一个
All right, I know one.
不过这个有点冷
But it's not funny.
洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
好，恩~一个去酒吧的家伙，对吗？
All right, well, a guy walks into a bar, right?
-老天，哥们
-仅仅开玩笑，不不不
- Jesus, man.
- Just kidding. No, no, no.
我有个更给力的，给力的哦
I got a good one. I got a good one.
是先有鸡还是先有蛋？
What comes first, the chicken or the egg?
答案是公鸡
The rooster.
晕~我擦~看见了吧？我太挫了
Oh, shit, see? I'm terrible.
这就是你最好的？
That's the best you got?
-是的，好吧...
-这个笑话有点冷
- Yeah, well...
- That's not funny.
我告你不冷
I told you it wasn't.
你一直都在想那个？
You ever think about that, though?
关于什么的？
About what?
你懂的，关于哪个先有的问题
You know, about what comes first.
我需要在乎什么吗？
What do I care?
-我杞人忧天了
-好吧
- I got more important shit to worry about.
- All right.
好吧，你真是碉堡了，你知道的
Well, you're a big deal, you know.
你有很重要的事情做，对吗？
You got important things to do, right?
你是做什么的？
What do you do?
我做我需要做的
Whatever I have to.
好吧，说实话，现如今混口饭吃不容易
Yeah, well it's tough making a living, that's for sure.
你有什么困难？
What do you know about tough?
和旁边那哥们一样困难，我想
As much as the next guy, I guess.
像一个未婚老妈一样困难？
How about as much as an unmarried mother?
几个意思？
What does that mean?
我写忏悔书的，四美分一个单词
Four cents a word, I write confession stories.
“未婚老妈”是我笔名
"The Unmarried Mother" is my pen name.
你没耍我？
Are you serious?
是啊
Yeah.
额~好吧
Right. Right!
那你生意如何？
How's business?
生意还凑合，我有一个周刊专栏
Business is okay. I have a weekly column.
我写，他们打印，我靠这个吃饭
I write them, they print them, I eat.
是吗？
Right?
-啥？你读过我的文章？
-是的
- What, you read my work?
- Yeah, yeah.
把你吓着了？
Does that surprise you?
-是的，一点点吧
-为什么
- Yeah, a little.
- Why?
你不符合样本
You don't fit the demo.
样本？
The demo?
-人口统计学样本
-是的，是的
- The demographic.
- Right. Right.
你知道，那些想感觉好受一些的离婚女
You know, broken women who want to feel better
通过读一些纸上写着的
about their pitiful lives by reading
悲惨故事或者背叛的经历
hard luck stories of heartbreak and betrayal
来慰藉心灵，这些光滑的书页
spewed across the glossy pages
只是25美分的纸浆烂泥
of 25 cent pulp sludge.
是的，没错！
Yeah, exactly.
好吧，额~你不觉得你现在生活有点苦逼？
Yeah, well you're being a little hard on yourself, don't you think?
真是一团糟
It's garbage.
我想我有些讲故事的天赋，但是我和谁开玩笑呢？
I thought I had some talent telling stories but who am I kidding?
我意思是，你告诉我，你已经读过他们了
I mean, you tell me. You've read them.
我得承认我只读过一点点
I have to admit I've had a few
黑夜里，当我以一点点女性的视角
dark nights when I've looked to you for a little
来看你
insight into the feminine mind.
你知道，对我而言你就像女性视角的一个热门产品
You know, it seems to me you've got a real hit on the woman's angle.
-女人的角度？
-是的
- Woman's angle?
- Yeah.
是的，我知道女性视角
Yeah, I know the woman's angle.
我应该是的。
I should.
为什么？你结婚了？你有妹妹么？
Why, you married? You got sisters?
如果我告诉你，你不会相信的。
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
这个工作告诉我一件事
The one thing that this job has taught me
就是真相比虚构要奇怪得多
is that truth is stranger than fiction.
我听过一些难以置信的玩意
I have heard some incredible shit.
没有什么能让我大吃一惊的
Nothing astonishes me anymore.
你不知道难以置信意味着什么
You don't know what incredible means.
是吗？好，来，试试看？
Yeah? Well, try me.
就是这样，我明白了
Here you go. I got that.
忘了它吧，哥们。我不会告诉你的
Forget it, man. I'm not telling you.
你害怕它不够好
You're scared it's not good enough.
-你觉得这个管用吗？
-是的
- You think that'll work?
- Yeah.
我们是什么？12岁小孩吗？
What are we, 12?
来吧
Come on.
我赌你那瓶剩下的酒，我这有你从未听过的最劲爆的故事
Bet you the rest of that bottle I got the best story you ever heard.
赌一整瓶
Bet you a full bottle.
你说什么？
What do you say?
如果我输了呢？
If I lose?
仅仅给20美分的小费
Just add a 20 to the tip.
为什么不呢？
Why not?
嘿，伙计
Hey, man.
-两扎
-好
- Two Buds, bud.
- Right.
Mayor Davidson,你怎样回应事实？
Mayor Davidson, how do you respond to the fact
许多纽约人离开了这个城市
that many New Yorkers are leaving the city
出于害怕闪灭炸弹人
in fear of a fifth attack by the Fizzle Bomber?
我们有额外的警队巡逻
We've got extra police patrols
24小时循环整个城市
on 24 hour shifts around the city.
我们和联邦炸弹小组联合，简历了任务部队
We've created a joint task force with the Federal Bomb Squad
FBI也接到命令抓捕嫌犯.
and the FBI in order to track down the suspect.
多么小白的名字
What a stupid name.
“闪灭炸弹人”
"Fizzle Bomber."
这家伙做了压缩三次甲基三硝基胺混合爆炸物
The guy makes compressed RDX-based explosive compounds.
这可不简单
That's not easy.
“闪灭炸弹人”很容易记住
"Fizzle Bomber" is easier to remember.
我增恨那个名字
I hate that name.
就像他的炸弹在嘶嘶作响
Makes it sound like his bombs just fizzle.
就像他们没有做任何破坏
Like they don't do any real damage.
我不认为任何人都在怀疑
I don't think anybody's doubting
这哥们的危险性
how dangerous this asshole is.
好吧，有很多傲慢自大的傻X需要教训教训
Well, there's a lot of selfish assholes out there needing a good shake up.
他们应该感到害怕
They should be afraid.
好吧，他已经杀了112个人了
Well, he's killed 112 people already.
一些人正在被计划杀掉中
Some people just gotta go.
阻止这个家伙
Stops the gene pool right in its tracks.
是的
Yeah.
也许他在帮这个城市一个忙
Maybe he's doing the city a favor.
你说这话当心被别人听见
Better be careful who hears you say that.
什么，你认为我说错了？
What, you think I'm wrong?
我仅仅说刚才那种谈话会让你惹麻烦
I'm just saying that kind of talk can get you in trouble.
没有比我之前的遭遇更惨的了
No worse than I've already been through.
听着，你一直向我保证这是我一生最好的故事
Now listen, you keep promising the best story of my life.
但是我没听到任何实质内容
But I'm not hearing anything.
好好
All right.
我想我将开始说了
Guess I'll start at the beginning.
当我还是个小女孩的时候...
When I was a little girl...
啥？
What?
什么，你想我告诉你我的故事？
What, you want me to tell my story?
不，我仅仅是，我想...
No, I just, I thought...
抱歉，好吧，恩~你继续
I'm sorry. Yeah, sure. Go on, go on.
当我还是个小女孩的时候...
When I was a little girl...
你曾经听过过Christine Jorgense吗？
You ever hear of Christine Jorgensen?
Roberta Cowell？
Roberta Cowell?
是的，是的，他们
Yeah, yeah, they had
OOXX了
sex change.
所以你...
So you...
甭打断哥。
Don't interrupt.
那是1945年9月13日
It was September 13th, 1945.
我当时只是个弃儿
I was a foundling.
一个留在孤儿院台阶上的新生儿
A newborn left on an orphanage doorstep.
克利夫兰市孤儿院
City of Cleveland Orphanage.
真是个好女孩
That's a good girl.
嗯~这小孩没有任何外部创伤痕迹
Well, there's no signs of trauma or exposure.
孩子显得恨健康
The child appears healthy.
如果她表现出任何感染或者过量的咳嗽
If she shows any signs of infection or excessive coughing,
她就需要带到医院来进行彻底检查
she should be taken to the hospital for a thorough examination.
是的，医生
Yes, Doctor.
她有名字么？
She got a name?
Jane。
Jane.
现在应该就叫她Jane吧。
Jane will have to do for now.
一周后我会回来检查Jane的身体情况。
I'll be back to check on Jane in a week.
我会照看好她
I look forward to it.
不要担心，我的小呀小苹果！
Don't worry, sweetheart.
我们会照看好你的
We'll take good care of you now.
我仅是那些没有过去历史芸芸众宝贝之一
I was just one of a dozen babies who had no past.
但是那是我们的共性之一
But that was all we had in common.
我从不生病，一天都没有
I was never sick, not one day.
因此我从没被带去过医院
So I was never taken to a hospital.
一直到我后来
Not until later in my life.
慢点
Slow down.
一个巧克力冰激凌
One chocolate ice cream
-给这可爱的小女孩
-谢谢
- for the cute little lady.
- Thank you.
当我很小的时候，我嫉妒那些有父母的小孩
When I was little, I envied kids with parents.
我憧憬着有父母是啥样
I always wondered what it would be like.
二B小孩
Stupid kid!
从该死的街上滚走！
Get off the damn street!
小赤佬！
Little shit!
Jane！
Jane!
过来。
Come here now.
婊子养的~
Son of a bitch!
我从来没有明白为什么我父母抛弃了我
I never understood why my parents abandoned me.
我做错了什么？
What had I done that was so wrong?
但是当我长大了一点，我知道了一些关于我的不同
But as I got older, I knew something was different about me.
性别搞混了我，你知道吗？
Sex confused me, you know?
它工作方式，它的适应方式
The way it works, the way everything fits.
我觉得不同
I felt different.
即使以后，我知道我有点不同
And even back then, I knew that I was going to be different
同其他女孩
from all the other girls.
我郑重发誓
I made a solemn vow
任何我的小孩将既有父母也有爸爸
that any kid of mine would have both a mom and a pop.
一个真正的家庭
A real family.
它使我纯洁
It kept me pure.
从引诱中逃离
Away from temptation.
因此我集中注意力关注那些更加重要的事情
So I focused my attention on more important things.
比如学习如何战斗
Like learning how to fight.
打！打！
Fight! Fight!
-来吧，Lucy，跑！
-来吧！
- Come on, Lucy, go!
- Come on!
你叫我什么？
What'd you call me?
粉红的，四眼，小婊子...
Pinky, four-eyed, little bitch...
我很坚忍
I was tough.
比其他小孩更加强壮
Much stronger than any of the other kids.
即使是男孩
Even the boys.
好，击碎它
All right, break it up!
-Jane，跟我来！
-我们走！
- Jane, come with me!
- Let go!
-你怎么了？
-我没做任何事情！
- What's wrong with you?
- I didn't do anything!
我也很聪明
And I was smart too.
班级第一
Top of the class.
等于...
Equals...
Jane！
Jane!
Jane.
你怎样期待去学会全部那些你从未...
How do you ever expect to learn anything if you never...
Fifteen.
数学和物理是我最喜欢的科目
Math and physics were my favorite subjects.
-回答正确。
-对于我很容易.
- That's correct.
- It all came easy for me.
雅蠛蝶
Retard.
够了
Enough!
当我更大一些的时候，
When I got older,
我意识到我到了结婚的机会
I realized I stood little chance of getting married
也是我被遗弃的同样的原因
for the same reason I hadn't been adopted.
我是不同的
I was different.
一个怪人，一个十足屌丝
A freak. A goddamn loser.
我停下来看镜子
I stopped looking in the mirror.
我恨我看见的
I hated what I saw.
我没有小时候小女孩的我的照片
I have no photos of myself as a young girl.
我甚至不记得我当时长啥样了
I don't even remember what I looked like.
现在这仅仅是一种感觉了
It's just more of a feeling now.
额~你看起来比我好多了
Well, you look better than I do.
谁会在乎酒吧老板长相？
Who cares how a barkeep looks?
或者就此而言一个作者
Or a writer for that matter.
但是你知道它是怎么回事
But you know how it is.
人们想接受一个小金发傻瓜
People want to adopt a little golden-haired moron.
并且接着，男孩子们
And later on, the boys,
他们想着大波和霹雳红唇
they want big tits and pouty lips.
你懂的，完美的那个
You know, perfect accessory.
我无法完成
I couldn't compete.
Jane，
Jane,
Mr. Robertson 做了一个特别的努力
Mr. Robertson has made a special effort
今天去和我们一些毕业的女孩子谈话
to talk to some of our graduating girls today.
你将很有礼貌的去听他说什么
You will do him the courtesy of listening to what he has to say.
Jane，我为一个新的组织工作
Jane, I work for a new organization
找年轻的女孩，像你这样的
seeking young women, like yourself,
训练他们为政府服务
to train in a career in government service.
我们是你们所谓的
We are what you might call
改革者
progressive.
我听说你对空间旅行很感兴趣
I hear you're interested in space travel.
额~他们说女人不能够当宇航员
Well, they say that girls can't be astronauts.
这是事实
That's true.
我们在找年轻的女士，能够展示出极大地希望
We're seeking young ladies who show great promise
不仅在数学和科学领域
in the fields of mathematics and science,
也在生理方面很强
as well as strong physical abilities.
我听说你有点喜欢私下争吵
I hear you're a bit of a backyard brawler.
这是在一个时代，衣着最终
This was around the time the suits
承认你不能够送男人进入太空几个月或者几年
finally admitted you can't send men into space for months or years
并且不能做一些缓解紧张情绪的事情
and not do something to relieve the tension.
他们正在寻找相当数量的类型
They were looking for respectable types,
完美的处女
preferably virgins.
他们可能尝试训练她们
They liked to train them from scratch.
超过平均精神和稳定感情的.
Above average mentally and stable emotionally.
但是大多数志愿者是妓女
But most of the volunteers were hookers
或者是离开地球10天就崩溃的精神病患者
or neurotics who would crack up 10 days off Earth.
她们不特别
They weren't special.
放松， Jane.
Just relax, Jane.
一些在你前面的女的有点紧张
Some of the ladies before you got a little nervous
有点思维混乱
a little lost in thought.
或许那是因为对于她们而言是一个陌生的领域
Perhaps that's because to them a thought is unfamiliar territory.
你觉得这个听上去像笑话吗？
Do you see this as some kind of joke?
是的，先生
No, sir.
我们这里已经有一些这些女性解放的类型
We've had some of these Women's Lib types in here
导致大混乱
causing a big fuss.
但是那不是你，是Jane对吗？
But that's not you, is it Jane?
是的，先生
No, sir.
请把你的眼镜拿下
Please take your glasses off.
我看你过去经有一些纪律问题
I see you've had some disciplinary problems in the past.
我没有任何问题，从第一年起我就像其他人一样“直”
I've had nothing but straight As in all my classes since the first grade.
是的
Yes.
你曾经和一个男人在一起？
Have you ever been with a man?
有吗？
Have you?
你明白这个招募要求你什么吗？
You understand what this employment will require of you?
我将能去太空么？
Will I get to travel into space?
如果你被选中，我想是的
If selected, yes.
没有
No,
我从未和男人在一起过
I haven't been with a man.
你怎样看待你这次旅行中担任的角色？
How do you see your role on this journey?
我的角色？
My role?
好吧，很多我们面试的女性觉得这是个已付费的假期
Well, many of the girls we've interviewed see this as a paid vacation.
一个很好地机会去过好日子，去和白马王子见面
A chance to live the good life and meet the man of their dreams.
你看待你自己像个旅行者么？
Do you see yourself as a tourist
或者一个参与者？
or a participant?
我在高等物理，生物学和太空学方面非常优秀
I've excelled in advanced physics, biology and astronomy.
一个旅行者是一个
A tourist is someone who
穿越大洋，仅仅被拍到坐在紧邻他们的船旁
travels across the ocean only to be photographed sitting next to their boat.
我没有意向成为一个旅行者
I have no intention of being a tourist.
如果他们接受我，他们必须教会我如何走和跳舞
If they accepted me they'd teach me how to walk and dance
并且，你知道
and, you know,
怎样去欢喜地听一个男人
how to listen to a man pleasingly.
加上用于初期关税的训练
Plus training for the prime duties.
对于我们的男孩而言没有一个是好的，对吗？
Nothing's too good for our boys, right?
他们保证在你征募期间不会让你怀孕
They made sure that you didn't get pregnant during your enlistment.
在你的故障排除后，你几乎肯定结婚
You were almost certain to marry at the end of your hitch.
就像和今天的空姐嫁给宇航员一样
Same way today's Flight Angels marry Spacers.
好吧，他们有共同语言
Well, they talk the same language.
是的
Right.
他们给了我隐形眼镜
They gave me contact lenses.
我从未看的如此清晰
I'd never seen the world so clearly before.
他们测试我们的忍耐力
They tested our endurance.
确保我们适合太空旅行
Made sure we were fit for space travel.
很多女孩子很挣扎
Many of the girls struggled.
除了我
Not me.
你多久OOXX？
How often do you think about sex?
A，一点也不。B，很少的
A, not at all. B, rarely.
C，有时候，D，经常
C, sometimes. D, often.
E，任何时候？
E, all the time?
C，有时候
C, sometimes.
D，经常
D, often.
这种测试持续了好几个月
The testing went on for months.
他们测试了我们方方面面
They tested us on everything.
许多女孩子失败了
Many girls failed.
除了我
Not me.
我从没见过这么高的分数
Highest numbers we've ever seen.
你感到压抑么？
Do you ever feel depressed?
-你啥意思？
-悲伤
- What do you mean?
- Sad.
总是空虚
Empty at times.
有时候...
Sometimes...
我想我感到有东西失去了平衡
I guess I feel like there's something out of balance.
就像我在另一个身体里或者似的
Like I'm living in somebody else's body.
难以言表（这里应该是在说“大姨妈”）
I don't know how to describe it.
没有一个女孩子像我
And none of the girls here like me.
你只需要给它一些时间
You'll just need to give it some time.
他们就会回来
They'll come round.
到她背后
Get her back!
-来吧！
-跑，Marcy！
- Come on!
- Go, Marcy!
来吧
Come on!
来吧，Marcy！
Come on, Marcy!
-扔她下来！
-打她背！
- Throw her down!
- Hit her back!
-嘿！
-嘿，离开她！
- Hey!
- Hey get off her!
-离开！
-停！
- Get off!
- Stop!
我们施行了更多患者生理检查
We have performed a more detailed physical examination of the patient.
我知道
I see.
你知道这将取消她的资格
You do know that this will disqualify her.
你没有告诉再招募？
You've not told the recruit?
-没有
-别这样。
- No.
- Don't.
我会处理好它
I'll take care of it.
我不明白
I don't get it.
我仅仅是自我防御，我应该怎么办？
I was just defending myself. What was I supposed to do?
我知道
I know.
相信我，这还没完
Believe me, it's not over yet.
我会去委员会上诉
I'll go to the Board of Appeals.
我将会做一切使你再招募
I'll do everything to get you reenlisted.
我向你保证
I promise.
相信我，Jane
Trust me, Jane.
而这就是这样了
And that was it.
由于我的一个愚蠢的打斗
Because of a stupid fight I was done.
我不得不自力更生
I had to support myself.
我不能够指望Roberton先生的承诺来看我通过
I couldn't rely on Mr. Robertson's promise to see me through.
- 你是个巫师？
- 那正是我想试着告诉你的
- You're a witch?
- That's what I've been trying to tell you.
为了挣钱我作为一个母亲的助手而工作
To earn money I worked as a mother's helper.
这个家庭仅仅想要一个便宜的仆人
This family simply wanted a cheap servant.
那就是当我第一次发现忏悔故事的时候
That was when I first discovered confession stories.
我不关心他们是否真实或者虚假
I didn't care if they were real or fake.
他是一个很好地方式消磨时间
It was a great way to pass the time.
白天我做家务
I did housework during the day
晚上我去上学
and went to school at night.
当在正式场合吃东西
When eating in formal situations,
放下你盘子里的刀叉
rest your knife and your fork on the plate
在满嘴食物或者说话的时候
between mouthfuls or to talk.
吸引课程是一种提高上诉委员会
Charm class was a way of proving to the Appeals Board
告知他们我礼仪端庄
that I was working on my decorum.
如果你吃完了你的食物
If you're finished with your meal...
这是第一次我没完成好事情
It was the first time I wasn't good at something.
当我不指望它的时候，
And when I wasn't expecting it,
我遇到了他。
I met him.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
他在那里
There he was.
你迷路了？
Are you lost?
他告诉我他在等人
He told me he was waiting for someone.
额~你知道俗话说机会是给准备好的人
Well, you know what they say about good things happening to those who wait.
“但收获的都是那些努力的人剩下的东西”，他说
"But only the things left behind by those who hustle", he said.
我不敢相信
I couldn't believe it.
这是林肯的名言
It was a quote by Abraham Lincoln
- 我正在想着同样的事情
- and I was thinking the exact same thing.
- I was thinking the exact same thing.
有什么区别？
What are the odds?
他是个高富帅。
He was handsome, rich.
他对待我很和蔼，我从没见过如这般小鲜肉
He treated me with a kindness that I'd never experienced before.
你知道，他实际上口袋里有100刀的账单
You know, he actually had wads of $100 bills in his pocket.
如此多的钱我这辈子都没见过
More money than I'd seen in my whole life.
他告诉我他会照看好我
He told me he'd take care of me.
所有的都出现了，对吗？
All show, right?
- 你小心扑通扑通？
- 是的
- Do you shoot pool?
- Yeah.
随着闪灭炸弹人的攻击越来越大，
With the Fizzle Bomber
attacks becoming larger and larger,
许多纽约人害怕这种大规模爆炸不可避免
many New Yorkers fear a bombing of mass scale is inevitable.
超过10000人已经疏散到周边国家
Over 10,000 have already evacuated upstate into surrounding counties...
他与众不同
He was different.
我喜欢他
I liked him.
他是第一个不和我玩游戏就能感觉很好的男人
He was the first man who was nice to me without playing games.
我年轻，坠入爱河
I was young and in love.
最后一句很有名
Famous last words.
你有没做过为爱付出的什么蠢事？
Haven't you ever done something stupid for love?
有一次
Once.
所以你醒悟了
So you understand.
是的
I do.
我万没料到它会发生
I never thought it would happen.
为了某人而坠入爱河
Falling for someone.
所有我的那些保持纯洁的规则烟消云散
All my little rules about being pure went out the window.
快乐的日子总是短暂的
It was the happiest time of my life but it didn't last long.
一天夜里，
One night,
他让我坐下
he sat me down.
告诉我他在等一个时机
Told me to wait for a moment.
你准备去哪？
Where are you going?
他告诉我他很快回来
He told me he'd be right back.
然后呢？
And then?
然后就没有然后了~
And then nothing.
我再也没见过他
I never saw him again.
他一去不复返兮
He never came back.
额~也许他有一个好理由
Well, maybe he had a good reason.
好吧
Okay.
我不应该去承受它
I didn't deserve it.
我以某种方式说服我自己这全是为了变得最好
Somehow I'd managed to convince myself that it had been all for the best.
我没有真心爱过他。这只是一场游戏一场梦
I hadn't really loved him. It was just a fling.
我更加渴求重新加入太空计划
I was more eager than ever to rejoin Space Corp.
我已经让我的生活陷入低谷很多次
I'd been let down in my life so many times
干嘛我要好好学习天天向上，对吗？
why should I have gotten my hopes up, right?
接着有时候
Then sometimes
人们却让你惊讶
people surprise you.
我从来没有如此同你坦诚相待，Jane
I hadn't been entirely truthful with you, Jane.
关于什么，先生？
About what, sir?
为了去保护我们的国民
In order to protect our nation's citizens,
对于政府的某些所作所为
it's important we keep
保密是很重要的
certain government operations confidential.
你不同意吗？
Wouldn't you agree?
同意，先生
Yes, sir.
我为一些初衷不是为了
I work for an organization whose primary purpose
太空旅行的组织工作
is not space travel.
而它是不道德的
It's reshaping wrongdoings.
我们利用太空集团，在人群中
We use Space Corp, among others,
作为一种手段找到那些特别的人
as a means of finding people who are special.
他们就是你称作征募新兵的机构
They are what you might call a recruitment agency.
我不明白
I don't understand.
征募新兵机构的目的是什么？
A recruitment agency for what?
寻找具有超常的能力的人
For people with exceptional abilities.
像你这样的人
People like yourself.
却没有家庭
People without families.
没有相公、娘子和孩儿
Without husbands and wives and children.
没有过去
No past.
没有同未来的联系
No ties to the future.
如你所见，我们的工作也已完成
You see, the work we do is complicated
需要雇员具有
and it requires employees with
高级机动的技术，出色的记忆
advanced motor skills, remarkable memories.
这是一个为了最好最牛比的人的工作
It's a job for the best and the brightest.
为了精英
For the elite.
精英？
The elite?
我无法相信
I couldn't believe it.
貌似我有个大好前程似的
Seemed like I had a bright future ahead of me.
我却不明白这份工作意味着什么
I didn't really understand what the job meant.
他们非常隐蔽和秘密，但
They were very covert and secretive but
我知道它将给我更好的生活
I knew it would change my life for the better.
并且他们不再有处女情结
And they didn't insist on virgins.
他们与太空集团不同
They were different to Space Corp.
直到我裙子变紧我才意识到我的未来完蛋了
It wasn't until my skirts got tight that I realized my future was over.
你怀孕了？
You were pregnant?
是的，你不知道？
Yeah, wouldn't you know it?
高富帅离我而去，丢我一人在这吹冷空气
My mystery man had left me with more than just a broken heart.
说好的明亮未来呢？精英女孩呢？
So that bright future, that girl who was elite?
她走了~
She was gone.
我再也没见过Robertson先生。
And I never saw Mr. Robertson again.
无路可退时，我到了一家慈善病房
With nowhere to go I landed in a charity ward
被其他各种大肚婆和小跑夜壶环绕
surrounded by other big bellies and trotted bedpans
终于轮到我了
until my time came.
我从未如此孤独
I never felt so alone.
一天夜里我发现我在手术台上，而一个护士对我说...
One night I found myself on an operating table with a nurse saying...
放松，Jane，放松
Relax, Jane. Relax.
现在请深呼吸
Now breathe deeply.
你赶脚如何？
How do you feel?
忒累了
Tired.
这很正常
That's natural.
破腹产很困难
A cesarean can be difficult.
你度过了危机
You pulled through fine.
破腹产？医生，我的小苹果还好吗？
A cesarean? Doctor, is my baby okay?
你的宝贝很好！
Your baby's fine.
男的女的？
Is it a boy or a girl?
是个健康的小女孩
It's a healthy little girl.
7磅3盎司
Seven pounds three ounces.
你知道这样...
You know it's something...
...生小孩
...to have made a baby.
我记得我得加个允许“女士”条例
I remember thinking I would tack on the admission form "Mrs."
告诉他他爹挂了
Let her think her papa was dead.
没有孤儿院接收我小孩
No orphanage for my kid.
但是外科医生仍在聊天
But then the surgeon kept talking.
这是嘛玩意，医生？
What is it, Doctor?
你丫之前有没有彻底检查过？
Have you ever had a thorough examination before?
是的
Yes.
医生告诉你什么？
What'd the doctors tell you?
啥也没有
Nothing.
我认为一切都很好
I thought everything was fine.
所以没有医生告诉过你
So no doctor's ever told you that
你身体内部构造
your internal set up
与大多数人不同？
was different than most?
没有
No.
你们在说啥？
What are you talking about?
为什么？
Why?
你没听那个苏格兰医师说吗？
Did you ever hear about that Scottish physician?
她35岁前是个女的
She lived as a female till she was 35,
然后她接受手术变成法律和医学上的男人了？
and then she had surgery and became legally and medically a man?
她结婚了，一切都很好。
She got married. Everything was okay.
打算对我怎么做？
What's that got to do with me?
当我们在实施手术时，我们发现一些非常独特的地方
When we performed your operation we found something very unique.
实际是一种
One of a kind, actually.
在我成功取出你小孩后，也即主要外科手术
After I successfully removed your baby I called for the Chief of Surgery.
我们磋商和工作了数小时
We held consultation and we worked for hours
力所能及把你重构
to reconstruct you the best we could.
重构？
Reconstruct?
你有两种器官，Jane
You had two full sets of organs, Jane.
女人和男人的
Female and male.
两者都不成熟
Both immature
但是女性器官
but the female set
很好地成长，使你可以有小孩
well enough developed for you to have a baby.
但是恐怕，亲，
But I'm afraid, my dear,
过量的生育出血
the excessive bleeding from the birth
逼着我们进行了子宫切除
forced us to perform a hysterectomy.
我们不得不阉了你的女性卵巢和子宫
We had to remove your ovaries and uterus.
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
但是至于重构
But the reconstruction
允许我们创建一个男性泌尿系统
allowed us to create a male urinary tract.
进一步外科手术还会继续
Further surgeries will be required.
变成男的？
To become a man?
你坑爹啊？
Is this some kind of joke?
我想我没坑爹
I'm afraid it's not.
你还年轻
You're young.
你的骨骼将会重新适应
Your bones will readjust.
我们将监控你的荷尔蒙平衡
We'll watch your hormonal balance.
这不是宣告死亡
It's not a death sentence.
你的生活可以继续
Your life can continue.
你是俺这辈子见过的最吊炸天的事情
You're the best thing that's ever happened to me.
你想过名字吗？
Have you thought of a name yet?
额~我正在想Jane，
Well, I was thinking of Jane,
在她母亲以后
after her mother.
我想这是为了在家里留存英名的一种方式
I guess it was a way of keeping the name in the family.
毕竟，我知道最终我将改变我自己的（名字）
After all, I knew eventually I would have to change mine.
这是个好名字
That's a good name.
我的感受变成了冷酷的决心
My feelings changed to cold determination.
我得做些对我的宝贝Jane一些的好事
I had to do right by my baby Jane.
但是两周后，什么也不是了
But two weeks later that didn't mean anything.
为啥？
Why?
他被夺走了
She was snatched.
-夺走了？
-是的
- Snatched?
- Yeah.
“夺走了”？你啥意思啊？
What do you mean "snatched"?
就是拐走了
Kidnapped.
从该死的医院护士病房被偷走了
Stolen from the goddamn hospital nursery.
我意思是那个男人是怎么来把弄走的？
I mean how's that for taking the last a man's got to live for?
当护士背过身，有个人走进来
When the nurse had her back turned, someone walked in
并且带着她走出去
and walked out with her.
没有任何线索？
Were there any clues?
抑或是任何描述？
Any description?
就一男的
Just a man.
脸型嘛，
With a face-shaped face.
像你或者像我这种
Like yours or mine.
不！不！
No! No!
有可能是孩子他爹
Could have been the baby's father.
护士发誓，说是个老头但是谁又会偷我的小孩？
The nurse swore it was an older man but who else would swipe my baby?
你做了神马？
What'd you do?
填了一个人口失踪单子
Filed a missing person's report.
检查收容机构，孤儿院。凡是你能说出来的，我都找了
Checked adoption agencies, orphanages. You name it, I did it.
但毫无结果
But nothing.
就像她消声觅迹了一般
It's like she vanished.
他们没找到那家伙？
And they never found the guy?
从来没有
Never.
但随后我的其他小问题却找上门来了
But then my other little problem began to take center stage.
Jane，我想从我这里倒数10下
Jane, I want you to count backwards from 10 for me.
10,9，8，
Ten, nine, eight,
7，6，5，4，...
seven, six, five, four...
我花了11个月在那个该死的地方
I spent 11 months in that fucked-up place
接受了三次大手术
and had three major operations.
我开始吃睾丸激素
I started taking testosterone,
使得我的声音深沉一点
which deepened my voice a little bit
但是也不够那么深沉
but not enough.
因此我开始练习像男人那样说话
So I started practicing talking like a man.
你好
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
你好，很高兴见到你
Hi, nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你，今天天气真好
Nice to meet you. It's a lovely day.
你好，很高兴见到你
Hi, nice to meet you.
天气真好
It's a lovely day.
虽然我从没做的到位
I never could get it right, though.
你好
Hi.
我叫Jane
My name is Jane.
我名字叫Jane
你好，见到你很高兴
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
我叫Jane
My name is Jane.
我叫...
My name is...
我总是很害怕照镜子，看见镜中的我看着自己
I was always afraid to look in the mirror and see the person looking back at me.
我尽力规避
I held off as long as I could.
现在，却再也没事了
Now, it didn't matter anymore.
我认识的那个人已经走了
The person I knew was truly gone.
陌生了
Strange.
每次我看见自己的新面容
Every time I looked at my new appearance
我提醒自己那些毁掉我人生的王八蛋
I was reminded of that bastard that ruined my life.
我想这是某种混乱的讽刺
That's some messed up irony I guess.
有趣的是
The funny thing was
那些护士
the nurses,
她们认为我玉树凌风，潇洒迷人
they thought I was quite handsome.
是的
Yeah,
一个该死的讽刺
a fucking catch.
好，好，好
Right, right, right.
我想我也知道女人们想听到的
I guess I also knew what women wanted to hear.
祝贺，对吗？
Compliments, right?
是的
Right.
好吧，
Well,
貌似你长出来很完美
it seems to me you came out okay.
长出来很好？
Came out okay?
额~你知道，我想说
Well, you know, I just mean
你似乎像一个
you just seem like a,
你懂的，一个正常男人
you know, a normal man.
是的
Yeah.
再正常不过了
More normal than ever now.
什么个程度呢？意味着什么？
How so? What's that mean?
好吧，我刚发现今早
Well, I just found out this morning that
我不在打发空闲时间了
I'm not shooting blanks anymore.
额，好吧
Well, all right.
医生预言，我完全能够生育
Doctor's prognosis,
I'm a fully fertile male specimen.
好吧，让我第一个祝贺你
Well, let me be the first to congratulate you.
欢迎来到男人阵营
Welcome to the tribe.
你知道，有时候
You know, sometimes
我想这个世界受到狗屎风暴是罪有应得
I think this world deserves the shit storm that it gets.
我知道
I know.
我意思是，让我们面对他，没有人是无辜的
I mean, let's face it. Nobody's innocent.
每个人利用其它人去得到他想要的东西
Everybody just uses everybody else
to get what they want.
也许是
Maybe.
但也许又不是
Maybe not.
你听过“毁灭的女人”吗？
You ever hear the expression "a ruined woman"?
当然
Of course.
是的，我就是毁灭的女人
Well, I was as ruined as a woman could be.
我不在是女人了
I was no longer a woman
并且我不知道如何成为一个男人
and I did not know how to be a man.
好吧，这确实需要花时间适应
Well, it does take some getting used to.
你不明白
You have no idea.
我并非说学会穿衣或者如何说话
I don't mean learning how to dress or talk.
或者不走错洗澡间
Or not walking into the wrong bathroom.
你知道的，我该怎么活？
You know, how could I live?
我应从事什么职业？
What job could I get?
我不懂贸易
I didn't know a trade.
不会开车
Couldn't drive a car.
我憎恨离我而去的王八蛋
I hate that bastard for ripping out my heart
他毁了我的生活
and ruining my life.
他该死
He deserves to die.
所以我想过再去太空集团的应征
So I thought I'd reenlist in Space Corp.
这次去变成一个宇航员
This time to become an astronaut.
这很讽刺，我知道
It was ridiculous, I know.
他们有我的记录，我不能撒谎
They had my records. I couldn't lie.
一个人看着我，而我被标上了不适合基本训练的标签
One look at me and I was marked unfit for basic training.
我认为医生只是对我好奇而已
I think the doctor spent time on me just from curiosity.
他读了关于我的情况
He'd read about my case.
我绝望了
I was desperate.
我在寻找一个回去的路
I was looking for a way back in.
你知道，我终身被人叫做怪物
You know, I've been called a freak my whole life.
而我真的就是
Now I really was.
就像一个实验的小白鼠
Just a lab rat to be experimented on.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
-没事
-我就这样
- Yeah, right.
- I am.
我遇到很多人对我的遭遇表示遗憾
I've had a lot of people tell me how sorry they are for what happened to me.
我不想在听到这些了
I don't want to hear it anymore.
那你接下来想要啥？
Then what do you want?
每个人想要什么？
What does anyone want?
爱情
Love.
去他的爱情
Fuck love.
一个目的
A purpose.
目的？
A purpose?
你没有吗？
You don't have that?
我正为此而努力
I'm working on it.
那为何爱情不能成为一个目的？
Why can't love be a purpose?
那完全是扯蛋
Hippy bullshit.
恨比爱容易，对吗？
It's easier to hate than to love, right?
是的
Yeah.
很容易毁了某件事
It's easier to destroy something.
杀了某个人
Kill somebody.
你认为你能够做那些？
You think you could do that?
或许吧
Maybe.
我从你眼神中也看出来了
I see it in your eyes, too.
充满怨恨
That bitterness.
它能够接受
It can take over.
能够
It can.
好吧，你知道，逆水行舟
Well, you know if you don't move forward
不进则退
you fall backwards into a river of shit.
因此
So
不管如何，与其抑郁抱怨，担心未来
anyway, rather than getting angry and pissing away my entire future
不如坚持我的人生向前进
I knew I just had to get on with my life.
So
因此
我改了名字
I changed my name
来到了纽约
and came to New York.
我成为了一名油炸食品厨师
I got by as a fry cook
但是不仅辛苦，而且钱少
but the hours were long and the money was horseshit.
因此我买了个打字机，让我自己成为一个公共速记员
So I bought a typewriter and set myself up as a public stenographer.
多么可笑啊
What a laugh.
四个月间，我打了六封信，和一个手稿
In four months I typed six letters and one manuscript.
手稿是给 真实生活故事 而且纯粹浪费纸张
The manuscript was for Real Life Tales and a total waste of paper.
但是那个王八蛋写了卖了
But the jerk who wrote it, sold it.
使我萌生了一个想法
Which gave me an idea.
我买了一叠忏悔杂志，并且学习它们
I bought a stack of confession magazines and studied them.
文思泉涌
The words came easy.
“未婚的母亲”横空出世
The Unmarried Mother was born.
因此，现在你明白我是怎么以专业女性角度看待
So, now you know how I get the authentic woman's angle
一个未婚母亲的故事。
on an Unmarried Mother story.
虽然最终版本我还没有卖
Through the only version I haven't sold.
而真实是
The true one.
那么，我怎样赢得那瓶酒？
So, do I win the bottle?
不错
Not bad.
那么，就结了？故事结束了？
So, is that it? Story's over?
是的，我想恐怕是的
Yeah, afraid so.
那个毁了我的人生和我的的女儿的魔鬼
The man that ruined my life is a ghost and so is my daughter.
我想在某些点上你的让故事继续
I guess at some point you just gotta let things go.
不是吗？
And have you?
当然不行
Fuck no.
如果我把他摆到你面前？
What if I could put him in front of you?
那个毁了你一生的男人。
The man that ruined your life.
并且如果我能够像你保证
And if I could guarantee you
你最好逃离他
that you'd get away with it.
你会杀了他么？
Would you kill him?
发自内心的
In a heartbeat.
我知道他在哪
I know where he is.
是的，你当然知道
Yeah, of course you do.
不是扯蛋
No bullshit.
那你是怎么知道的啊？
And how the hell do you know that?
那里有记录
There are records.
医院记录，孤儿院记录，医疗记录...
Hospital records, orphanage records, medical records...
在那里，记着
Been there, done that.
Beth Fetherage。
Beth Fetherage.
不是那个在孤儿院看门的人名字？
Wasn't that the name of your caretaker at the orphanage?
Beth？
Beth?
你这狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
你以前跟踪我？
Have you been following me?
狗娘养的，这太搞笑了
Son of a bitch. That's funny.
不
No.
你的名字，作为一个女人，是叫Jane，对吗？
Your name, as a woman, was Jane, right?
你告诉我那个了，但是你没告诉我你作为男人的名字
You told me that. You didn't tell me your name as a man.
John。顺便说一句，这不是太新颖
John. Which is not terribly original, by the way.
你是谁？警察？还是其他什么人？
What are you, a cop or something?
我能把这家伙打趴
I can put this guy in your lap.
你可以想做什么就做什么
You can do whatever you want
并且我保证你会逃离他
and I guarantee you you'll get away with it.
好吧，他在哪？
All right, where is he?
我为你做了些事情
I do something for you
你就得为我做些什么
and you do something for me.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
好吧，那么，
Okay, well,
享受你的奖励
enjoy your prize.
我还能做什么？
What do I have to do?
你喜欢你的工作？
You like your job?
额~~当然不
Hell, no.
从来没有人给你一个喘息机会，对吗？
Nobody's ever given you a break, right?
你听过我的故事吗？
Did you listen to my story?
是的，在你服务训练期间你的优胜中
Yeah, and you excelled during your service training.
胜过的
Excelled.
你有一些你从来没有机会发挥的技能
You have skills you've never had the chance to use
而我能够给你那种机会
and I can give you that chance.
让我以这种方式放下
Let me put it this way.
我把他交给你，随你处置
I hand him to you, you do whatever you like.
事成之后，你来做我的工作
And when you're done, you try my job.
如果你不喜欢，你可以走人
You don't like it, you walk away.
你不会在讨论当酒吧侍者吧？
You're not talking about bartending are you?
我没有说关于酒吧侍者的事情
I'm not talking about bartending.
那是什么？
What is it?
到时候会给你看的
I'll show you.
不，去你的，不。
No. Fuck that, no.
别耍我了，有话直说
Stop playing games. Just tell me right now.
瞧，Robertson会比我解释的更加好。
Look, Robertson explains it so much better than I do.
不要惹我
Don't mess with me.
什么，你为Robertson工作？
What, you're working with Robertson?
是的，并且他希望我能够帮助你
Yes, I am, and he wants me to help you.
你隶属于Robertson的小秘密团体？
You're part of Robertson's little secret society?
是的
Yes.
告诉我关于他的全部。
Tell me what it's all about then.
先做重要的事情
First things first.
Jerry！我准备休息了
Jerry! I'm going on a break.
哦，妈的
Oh, fuck.
他在哪？
Where is he?
什么，他在那里倒下了？
What, is he down there?
听着，你仅仅是必须要相信我，好吗？
Listen, you're just going to have to trust me, all right?
我现在一定是醉了
Now I must be drunk.
你最好别耍我
You better not be fucking with me.
你想我是不是可能是闪灭炸弹人？
You think I might be the Fizzle Bomber?
有可能
Maybe.
假使你是闪灭炸弹人怎么样呢？
What if you're the Fizzle Bomber?
如果我是？
What if I am?
额~得了吧
Well, come on.
这就是你想的，对吗？
This is what you wanted, right?
来吧
Come on.
我的地盘我做主
I'm my own grandpa
我们走
Here we go.
好
All right.
在这跟紧我
Follow me right in here.
这些天别太大意了
Can't be too cautious these days.
你在做神马？
What are you doing?
你知道，杀了某人是不容易的
Killing somebody's not easy, you know.
不论多么仇恨气愤，你可能在你的心中
No matter how much hate and anger you may have in your heart,
当扣动扳机的那一刻来临
when it comes time to pull the trigger
大多数人做不到
most people can't do it.
你根据经历说的？
You speaking from experience?
我只是告诉你事实
I'm just telling you the truth.
好吧，我不害怕
Well, I'm not afraid.
你把他带过来给我，我绝不迟疑
You bring him to me and I won't hesitate.
好，这很好
All right, that's good.
那么，他人在哪？
So, where is he?
甭着急
Hold your horses.
啥？你丫逗我玩啊？
What, are you going to play for me?
不，不。我打算送你回到过去
No, no. I'm going to play you the past.
这是一个USFF协调转换域工具箱
This is a USFF Coordinates Transformer Field Kit.
不是电影桥段
No moving parts.
它重约六公斤，全充电状态
It weighs approximately six kilos, fully charged.
我已经调试他支持我的身体质量
I've adjusted it to support our body mass.
他将计算一个慎重的到达地点
It will calculate a discreet arrival location
并且避免任何物质碰撞
and avoid any materialization collisions.
那么，它是什么？
So, what is it?
他是一个构造当时醒来的装置
It's a device that creates a temporal wake.
一个啥？
A what?
这是一个时间机器
It's a time machine.
你丫在这里扯淡吧
You gotta be shitting me.
不，我没扯。
No, I am not.
瞧，不要被警报，行吗？
Look, don't be alarmed, all right?
你得站近点。
You have to stand closer.
你得在3英尺里面
You have to be within three feet.
你拿两把枪干嘛使？
What have you got two guns for?
甭担心
Don't worry.
哥干这行很多年
I've done this a lot.
说真的，兄弟，你别拿我开涮了
Seriously, pal, you need to stop playing games with me.
是男人挺住，好吧？
Stand still, okay?
深呼吸，hold住了！
Take a deep breath and hold this.
我hold住！没问题，你弄你的就是了
Hold it. It's okay. Here you go.
现在，你只要闭上眼睛。
Now, you just have to close your eyes.
为毛我要闭眼啊？
Why do I need to close my eyes...
-大爷的，那是什么？
-好！
- God, what was that?
- Yeah.
时间扭曲域
The time distortion field.
-你会很好的
-啥？
- You're going to be fine.
- What?
你丫的深呼吸就行了，别废话好吗？
Just take some deep breaths, all right?
这是啥？
What is this?
深呼吸，闭好你的眼睛！
Just take some deep breaths.
全世界都有最清新氧气！
The first few jumps can really knock you around.
-跳跃了？
-是的
- Jumps?
- Yeah.
我们在俄亥俄州克利夫兰，时间1963年4月3日
We're in Cleveland, Ohio, April 3rd, 1963.
什么？
What?
不可能
That's impossible.
我知道
I know.
瞧，在这个任务里，你不能犯任何错误
Look, in this job you can't afford to make any mistakes.
时间是关键。
Timing is essential.
我去给你搞点“毛爷爷”花花
I've got some money for you.
时间规划局才不管你花多少钱呢
The Temporal Bureau doesn't care how much money you spend.
和他们无关
It doesn't matter to them.
他们只是不喜欢任何没有必要进行时空跳跃的人
What they don't like is any unnecessary anachronisms.
时间规划局？
The Temporal Bureau?
是你效力的俱乐部吗？
Is that the company you work for?
是的，是那家你几乎要转会的公司
That's right. The one you almost worked for.
那么，Robertson人哩？
So, where's Robertson?
他在1985年
He's in 1985.
啥？
What?
在规划局总部
At Bureau headquarters.
那又怎样，你是个警察？
So what, you're a cop?
我是一个时间特工，11人小组之一
I'm a Temporal Agent, one of 11.
我们在犯罪发生之前阻止他们
We prevent crime before it takes place.
看，这有些衣服，穿上他们
Here. Here's some clothes.
Put them on.
额~你咋知道这会有衣服的？
Well, how did you know the clothes would be there?
无关紧要，我们只需要开始调配进就行
Doesn't matter. We just need to start blending in.
啥？你以前来过这？
What, have you been here before?
这一句话讲不清，好吧
It's complicated, all right?
好吧，我狗不理
Yeah, no shit.
瞧，我们的时间上的破坏
Look, our time disruption footprint
需要非常小
needs to be extremely small.
时间规划局允许轻微的变化
The Bureau allows for slight variations
但是最终的参数确是很严格的哦
but ultimately the parameters are extremely strict.
任何我们任务的偏差会导致终结
Any deviation from our mission results in termination.
终结你的工作？
Termination of your job?
终结你的性命
Termination of your life.
这就是为啥你想在这个时间段内保持和人谈话
That's why you want to keep your conversations to people in this time period
到最低限度
to an absolute minimum.
这个时间段
This time period.
好。那么你最远能旅行多久？
Okay. So how far can you travel, then?
从零点开始前后53年
Travel beyond 53 years of zero point, either direction,
将会导致时间轨迹分解
will result in the temporal wake disintegrating.
零点？
Zero point?
开始时间旅行的地方
The invention of time travel.
那是什么时候？
And when's that?
将会是1981年
It will be in 1981.
好的
Right.
真难以置信
I can't believe this.
那么
And so,
我可能成为其中一份子，你知道的，一个时间特工？
I get to be one of these, you know, a Temporal Agent?
如果你证明你自己
If you prove yourself.
好。
Right.
那么这个对于你，这家伙是什么
So what's this guy to you?
嗯~我开始怀疑他就是闪灭炸弹人，是吗？
Well, I'm starting to suspect that he might be the Fizzle Bomber. All right?
但是很明显，他是你主要的棘手困难所在
But all that's clear is he's the main obstacle that's held you back.
因此，我杀了他
So, I kill him
你把我带去找Robertson
you take me to Robertson
然后给我看一切
and you show me everything.
成交
Agreed.
好，那么他在哪？
Right. Okay, so where is he?
好。嘿，嘿
Okay. Hey, hey.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
是的
Yeah.
好的，他在克利夫兰学院，从这里起五个街区
All right, he's at Cleveland College,
five blocks from here.
你记得？他在找Jane的路上，找你！
You remember? He's on his way
to meet Jane. You.
1963年的你
The 1963 you.
是的，我记得
Yeah, I remember.
好，太棒了
Okay, great.
那么，我能够做这个？我能改变我的过去？
So, I can do this?
I can change my past?
是的，你可以
Yes, you can.
你有想过改变你的过去吗？
Have you ever thought about changing yours?
我从不偏离我的任务
I never deviate from the mission.
-从不？
-从不
- Never?
- Never.
瞧，当你完事了，我去接你，好吗？
Look, I'll pick you up when you're done, all right?
不，谁？你去哪？
No. Whoa, where are you going?
不要担心，我很快回来，相信我
Don't worry. I'll be around, trust me.
我能...
Do I...
我有的选么？
Do I have a choice?
是的，你总是有选择的
Of course. You always have a choice.
是的，但是有时候你不认为是命中注定的么？
Yeah, but sometimes don't you think that things are just inevitable?
是的，这种想法我脑海中闪过
Yes, the thought has crossed my mind.
这就是人生
This life.
她孤单么？
Is it Ionely?
没有家庭
No family.
没
No.
但是，你确实有个目的
But, you do have a purpose.
是的
Right.
哦，我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry.
你迷路了？
Are you lost?
不，我在找一个人
No, I'm looking for someone.
谢谢，我仅仅在等待
Thanks, I'll just wait.
好，你知道他们说机会是给有准备的人的
Well, you know what they say about good things happening to those who wait.
但收获的都是那些努力的人剩下的东西
But only the things left behind by those who hustle.
我也是这么想的
I was thinking the exact same thing.
差别是什么？
What are the odds?
差别是什么。
What are the odds.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你不知道我是怎么想象你的容颜
You're not how I imagined you'd look.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
你真美
You're beautiful.
某人应该已经告诉过你了
Someone should have told you that.
是的，你刚才说过了
Well, you just did.
如果曾经想阻止闪灭炸弹人
If you ever want to stop the Fizzle Bomber
你将永远没有第二次机会
you'll never get another chance.
来吧，来吧
Come on, come on.
有时候你不觉得这是命中注定的么？
Sometimes don't you think that things are just inevitable?
是的，这种想法我脑海中闪过
Yes, the thought has crossed my mind.
时间旅行可以失去方向
Time travel can be disorienting.
即使小的时空跳跃也能造成蝴蝶效应
Even short jumps can knock you around a bit.
不要尝试跳跃极限
Don't ever exceed the jump limit.
会出问题的
It can be problematic.
深呼吸
Deep breaths.
这招总是管用
They always help.
我不出去，见很多新人
I don't get out and meet a lot of new people.
为什么不呢？
Why not?
我不知道，我只是不想
I don't know. I just don't.
你紧张了？
Are you nervous?
哦，是的
Oh, yeah.
不要忘了买顶帽子，手套和夹克
Don't forget to buy a hat, gloves and a jacket.
回到64年，这时候真冷啊
It's cold this time of year, back in '64.
这是一个工作，对吗？记住它
This is a job, all right? Remember that.
这个不像其他的，但是你仍然有任务在截止日前
It's unlike any other, but you still have tasks to perform
执行完
deadlines to meet.
一些日子里这些任务对于他人而言很容易
Some days those tasks are easier than others
但是你的成功确是很有必要的
but it's imperative that you succeed.
你总是知道这一天将要来临
You always knew this day would come.
你不能做这个
You can do this.
你为什么不去见新的人？
Why don't you meet new people?
我不善于社交
I'm not very good in social situations.
我想一些人也不像我
Some people just don't like me, I guess.
何出此言，你这么认为？
Why is that, do you think?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许是因为你觉得你比别人优秀
Perhaps it's because you think you're better than them.
我没听错吧？
Excuse me?
恩~你觉得你很优秀
Well, you think you're superior.
你去找谁...
Who the hell are you to...
你甚至不认识我
You don't even know me.
我错了么？
Am I wrong?
拿一个去了解另一个
Takes one to know one.
是的
True.
那么，什么使得你如此优越？
So, what makes you so superior?
我会读心术
I can read minds.
哦，真的？
Oh, really?
是的，完全可以
Yeah, absolutely.
好吧，此时此刻我在想啥？
All right, what am I thinking right now?
你在想
You're thinking,
优雅课程在这里不管用了
"Charm class isn't helping this situation."
哇，真的很神奇！
Wow. Amazing.
你在想
You're thinking,
为啥别人都能得到想要的，而我不行？
"Why does everyone always get what they want and I get nothing?
我总是各种苦逼
"That I'm tired of being tough all the time."
每个人都那么想
Everyone thinks that.
你假装爱情
You pretend like love
与你一点关系没有，而真相是
doesn't matter to you, when the truth is
你总是在渴望着
it's all you ever think about.
那不对！
That's not true.
好吧
Okay.
什么，你不相信我？
What, you don't believe me?
你仅仅只了解我一个小时而已
You've known me for a whole hour.
你从未坠入过爱河
You've never been in love.
那与你无关
That's none of your business.
这不能算一个回答
That's not an answer.
什么使你认为你应当得到一个（爱情）？
What makes you think you deserve one?
你说的很对
You're right.
对于我的直接，我很抱歉
I'm sorry for being so direct.
你说我不像你想象的那样
You said that I'm not how you imagined.
我们以前认识吗？
Have we met before?
不，我...
No, I...
我不知道为啥我会那么说
I don't know why I said that.
因为我感到我们有
Because I feel like we have.
生活对于你不容易吧，是不？
Things haven't been easy for you, have they?
每个人都有问题
Everyone's got problems.
Yeah.
是的
我们都会羁绊在人生路上
We all trip up along the way.
但是你和我，
But you and I,
或许跨越了同样的东西
perhaps over the same things.
Robertson先生，再次见到你很高兴
Mr. Robertson, it's good to see you again.
已经有一会了
It's been a while.
是的
Yes.
从你的角度，我认为是的
From your perspective, I suppose it has.
我不认为你能够再跳跃了
I didn't think you jumped anymore.
除非特殊情况发生
Only on special occasions.
我有了一片“闪灭炸弹人”定时器的碎片
I have a piece of the Fizzle Bomber's timer.
你进行了非法时空跳跃，这是很严重的过错。
You made an illegal jump. That's a serious offense.
这已经无关紧要了
It doesn't matter anymore.
我必须再试一把
I had to try again.
你理解他么？
And did you apprehend him?
不
No.
每次进行时空跳跃你身后留下的碎片
The fragments of matter you leave behind after each jump
我们只能修复很多
we can only repair so much.
开始精神、智障分析
The onset of psychosis, dementia.
这是认真的
It can be serious.
我很好
I'm fine.
你经历了多少次非法时空跳跃？
How many illegal jumps have you made?
就一次
Just one.
我将接受惩罚
I'll accept the punishment.
规划局参数设置很严格，这是有理由的
The parameters set by the Bureau are strict for a reason.
他们存在是为了保护我们
They exist for our protection.
然而
However,
我总是在想我们能够完成如此之多
I've always thought we could accomplish so much more
不受规划局委员会的限制
without the constant bureaucratic control of the board.
一个特种在外操作
An Agent operating from the outside.
她将经历如此多的痛苦，全赖我
She'll endure so much pain because of what I do.
这是命运的选择
That's the way it has to be.
这是命中注定
That's the way it's always been.
你应该比任何人都明白
You should understand that better than anyone.
蛇咬尾，无穷无尽
The snake that eats its own tail, forever and ever.
你在这里创造历史，影响未来
You are here to create history and influence what is to come.
我不认为我能做什么
I don't think I can do it.
明白
Understand
你不仅仅是一个特工
you are more than an Agent.
你有天赋
You're a gift
给予这个世界打破
given to the world through a
宿命悖论
Predestination Paradox.
你是唯一的一个人
You're the only one
从历史、祖先中解放
free from history, ancestry.
公鸡
The rooster.
但是你必须完成你的任务
But you must complete your mission.
你必须为未来埋下种子
You must lay the seeds for the future.
我们就全靠你了
We're counting on you.
而当什么发生了才能让我能有天不知道我的未来如何
And what happens when that day comes, when I have no knowledge of my future?
好吧，就像其他人一样
Well, then, like everyone else
你正准备某天某时不得不拿走她
you're just going to have to take it one day at a time.
你面前是一个很长的旅途
You have a long journey ahead of you.
他们说旅途有几千公里
They say that the journey of a thousand miles
千里之路始于足下
starts right at your feet.
而我的双脚能够用来休息
And my feet sure could use a rest.
好吧，仅仅闭上你的眼睛
All right, just going to cover up your eyes
仅仅为了安全，好吗？
just to be safe, okay?
时空跳跃超过20年会很困难
Jumping back almost 20 years can be rough.
抓紧这小孩
Hold the baby tight.
你准备好了吗？
You ready?
记住，深呼吸
And remember, deep breaths.
也许成功的关键是，不起眼的时间旅行
Preparation is the key to successful, inconspicuous time travel.
运气是设计的残留物
Luck is the residue of design.
早些年，我登记为Gregory Johnson
Earlier, I had registered as Gregory Johnson,
俄亥俄州沃伦
Warren, Ohio.
把它变得简单
Keep it simple.
融合在一起
Blend in.
安全到达，Jane
Safe journey, Jane.
保持强壮，John。
Stay strong, John.
你有一个远大前程。
You have a bright future ahead.
克利夫兰市孤儿院
City of Cleveland Orphanage.
待在这里
Stay here.
你去哪？
Where are you going?
不要担心
Don't worry.
我一会就回来
I'll be right back.
你相当讨厌
You sick fuck.
你耍我
You tricked me.
选择是你的
The choice was yours.
什么选择？
What choice?
我不打算离开她
I'm not going to leave her.
这就是这样，就这样了
That's the way that it is.
命里注定就这样的
It's the way it always has been.
如果你觉得被骗了，对不起
I'm sorry if you feel deceived.
但是我们能够改变某些事件，这是个错误。
But it's a mistake to think that we can change certain events.
就像你说的，某些东西是命中注定的
Just like you said, some things are inevitable.
-但是我爱她
-我知道
- But I love her.
- I know.
我知道是这样
I know that.
所以既然你找到了她
And now that you've found her
也知道她是谁
you know who she is.
并且你明白你是谁
And you understand who you are.
并且现在也许你准备明白我是谁了
And now maybe you're ready to understand who I am.
就现在，听我说，听我说。
Now, listen to me. Listen to me.
震动将会减弱
The shock will wear off
但是你知道这些事情以后能够安慰自己
but you can take comfort in knowing that these events
朝着正确的方向发展
are happening in the correct order.
你走的这条路将会带领你到达终点
The path you're on will take you to your destination.
那是哪里？
Where is that?
你让我带你去见Robertson，他会给你看一切
You let me take you to Robertson and he'll show you everything.
我不想离开她
I don't want to leave her.
你没有
You're not.
我从来没有想过去伤害她
I never wanted to hurt her.
我知道
I know.
而现在她也知道了
And now she knows too.
John。
John.
听我说好吗？你回家
Listen to me, all right? You're home.
你的麻烦就结了
Your troubles are over.
你打算拯救千万人的生命
You're going to save millions of lives.
你将从事对于一个男人而言最重要的工作
You're about to embark on the most important job a man has ever had.
而你将变得伟大，我知道
And you're going to do great. I know.
好了，他已经跳跃了22年。
All right, he's forward jumped 22 years.
他不习惯如此长的距离
He's not used to this kind of distance.
John不得不去想这些
John had to want this.
他的人生不得不搞得一团糟
His life had to be fouled up.
他不得不一无所有去完成这么多
He had to have nothing in order to achieve so much.
很多可怕的罪犯没有按计划进行，全因为他
A hundred horrible crimes didn't go as planned, because of him.
因为你做的这个工作
Because of the work you've done.
但是闪灭炸弹人仍然逍遥法外
But the Fizzle Bomber's still out there.
我失败了
I failed.
他使你成为了一个更好的特工
He made you a better Agent.
我们都从他身上学到了东西
We've all learned things from him.
他让我们工作的更好
He's made us better at our jobs.
这个机构不会增长
This organization wouldn't have grown
如果不是为了闪灭炸弹人
if it wasn't for the Fizzle Bomber.
你听上去好像你狠敬佩他
You sound as if you admire him.
他是个恐怖分子
He's a terrorist.
不会像那么简单的
Nothing's that simple.
我到希望简单呢
I wish that it were.
这是什么？
What's this?
这是一个定时器
It's the timer.
去一些新的引领者
Got some new leads.
当你到达了你最终的那一站时
When you reach your final destination
你的域工具箱将会退役...
your Field Kit will decommission...
就像每个规律一样
As per regulation.
你确定你想时空跳跃退役回纽约
You sure you want to retire to New York
离爆炸日子很近的那天么？
so close to the date of the blast?
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
你多保重
You take care of yourself.
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
我的地盘我做主
I'm my own grandpa
爷爷的，转角！
Jesus H. Christ, Conner!
这，看，我将会退还你们该死的钱
Here, look, I'll refund your goddamn money.
我不想要退款。就让我弹完这该死的一曲！
I don't want a refund. Just let me play the damn song!
好吧，来吧，Jerry。让他弹完这该死的曲子
Yeah, come on, Jerry. Let him play the damn song.
顺便说一句，我退出
And by the way, I quit.
那么，就这样了
So, this is it.
回家
Home.
最终的命令今天下来了
The order finally came through today.
我想是不可避免了
I guess it was inevitable.
伴着你听到这个，七年过去了
By the time you listen to this seven years will have passed.
我们第一个任务就像最后一个一样重要
Our first mission is just as important as our last.
每个任务使得我们更加接近最终目标
Each one getting us closer to our final destination.
瞧，你将找到那个时刻
See, you'll find out that time
对于像我们这样的人具有一个非常不同的意义
has a very different meaning to people like us.
时间抓住了我们所有人
Time catches up with us all
即使那些在我们行当里的人
even those in our line of work.
我想你可能会说我们天赋秉异
I guess you could say we're gifted.
上帝啊，这听起来是多么傲慢
God, Jesus, that sounds arrogant saying it out loud.
好吧，我将以一个更好的方式来说
All right, I'll put it a better way.
我想你可能会说
I guess you could say
我们与生俱来就是干这个的
we were born into this job.
你不会再看见很多人用这个了
You don't see a lot of guys using these anymore.
-你还好么？
-是的
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
这仅仅是...
It's just that...
我对于过去有点敏感
I get kind of sentimental about the past.
听起来很酷
That's cool.
我也是
Me too.
我知道
I see.
那么，你是个作家？
So, you're a writer?
我想我过去是
I used to be, I guess.
而你想重操旧业？
And you're thinking of taking it up again?
我想过这个
I was thinking about it.
-好吧
-恩
- Right on.
- Yeah.
你写什么样的东西？
What kind of things do you write?
嗯~仅仅是忏悔故事。
Oh, just confession stories.
啥？类似于那些轻蔑的妇女的故事？
What, kind of like those scorned women stories?
你知道，激情，心脏病，嫉妒
You know, passion, heartbreak, jealousy.
恩~不是一点像，就那玩意
No, not kinda like, exactly like.
-认真的？
-是的，我认真的
- Seriously?
- Yeah, seriously.
你看上去不像那种类型的人
You don't look like the type of guy that'd be into that.
那你觉得我应该像啥？
What do I look like I would be into?
这是个大问题
That's a big question.
好吧，你对这个华丽的皇家40款很感兴趣
Well, you're interested in this gorgeous '40 Royal Portable.
I am.
是的
这是小说家海明威，凯鲁亚克，弗莱明等人的选择。
Tool of choice for Hemingway, Kerouac, Fleming.
考虑到我认识你达到30秒...
And taking into account I've known you for a whole 30 seconds...
我认为你在冒险
I'm thinking you're into adventure.
悬而不决
Suspense.
也许是一种浪漫接触
Maybe a touch of romance.
而当然，一个大规模的谋杀
And definitely a big splash of murder.
-那很愚蠢，不是吗？
-是的，他不是
- That's stupid, right?
- No, it's not.
做回你可能成为的人，永远不迟
It's never too late to be who you might have been.
这不仅仅是生理上的伤害.
It's not just the physical injuries.
你已经积累了更多的小时
You've logged more field hours
超过了我先前安排的其他任何特工
than any of the other Agents I've been assigned to.
这个任务是真实的
The risks are real.
每次时空跳跃以后，你身后留下的碎片
The fragments of matter you leave behind after each jump
我们只能大肆修补
we can only repair so much.
开始心理、智障测试
The onset of psychosis, dementia.
这可是认真的
That can be serious.
我很好
I'm fine.
时间旅行能够让你迷失
Time travel can be disorienting.
别超过时间跳跃的极限
Don't ever exceed the jump limit.
会出问题的
It can be problematic.
蛇咬尾
The snake that eats its own tail
无穷无尽
forever and ever.
我知道我从哪里来
I know where I come from.
但是所有你们这些人来自哪里？
But where do all you zombies come from?
哦，偶滴神哪
Oh, my God.
你看起来很好
You look good.
哥我想你
I missed you.
你是闪灭炸弹人？
You're the Fizzle Bomber?
我们总是讨厌那个名字，记得不？
We always hated that name, remember?
你是个杀人犯
You're a murderer.
不，不，不。瞧见没，我拯救苍生超过在这个规划局里
No, no, no. See, I've saved lives, more than I ever could have
大肆屠杀
from inside the bureau.
不，你滥杀无辜
No, you kill innocent people.
无辜的人
Innocent people.
不，不，不
No, no, no.
我掌握未来的片段
I have clippings from the future.
这些片段从未发生过
Clippings from futures that never happened
因为我阻止了他们
because I prevented them.
更多的悲剧阻止了，生命被拯救下来
More tragedies prevented, lives saved.
你看见这个没？
You see this?
-拯救
-是的，是的，瞧
- Saved?
- Yeah, yeah. Look.
看，1974年，芝加哥化学泄露
Look. 1974, Chicago chemical spill.
那个司机从来没有在早晨成功工作过
That driver never made it to work in the morning.
而如今，324个生命得到救赎
Now, 324 lives saved.
看，看吧，接下来是什么？是什么？
Look, look. What's next? What's next?
好，恩~我们还有...在1991年4月3日，德国汉堡
Right, well we have... We have 1991,
April 3rd, Hamburg, Germany.
1861条人命得到救赎
1,861 lives saved.
Hardshaw武器工厂抢劫事件，1968年
The Hardshaw Weapons Factory Heist, 1968.
你知道，恐怖分子从来没进入大楼，因为我炸了它
You know, the terrorists never came in the building because I blew it the fuck up.
我救了3027条人命
3,027 lives I saved.
你数过你杀了的市民数量吗？
Do you keep count of all the civilians you killed as well?
你下次攻击将会使超过10000人命丧黄泉
Your next attack will kill 10,000 more.
你对我失望了，对吗？
You're disappointed in me, right?
我记得那个，是的
I remember that, I do.
但当尘埃落定
But when the dust settles
我觉得你将看见我们做了正确的事情
I think you'll see that we did the right thing.
我永远不会成为你
I will never become you.
不，我很好奇
No, I'm curious.
你上报过
Did you report
你的退役的时间机器没有退役？
that your decommissioned Field Kit didn't decommission?
对吗？
Right?
一些人说，那不是命运
Some people say that it's fate.
但是你和我
But you and I,
我们知道
we know
有些事情命中注定
some things are predestined.
我成就了你，你成就了我
I made you who you are. You made me who I am.
这是个悖论，对吗？
It's a paradox, right?
但是不能够被打破了
But it can't be paradoctored.
对吗？
Right?
我很高兴能先占有你，我确实这么想
I had so much fun at preempting you, I did.
而今你自由了却来找了我
And now you're free and you found me
我们可以一起打天下
and we can be together.
我才不屑成为你
I'll never become you.
别那么说
Don't say that.
我们只是傀儡
We're just puppets.
我们是Robertson
We are Robertson.
他策划了整件事
He set the whole thing up.
他玩弄我们于股掌之间
He played us for fools.
他触发了多米诺骨牌效应
He's laying out the dominoes.
你知道，咱们只能看着牌倒下去
You know, we're just watching it fall.
我不会变成你
I will never become you
我也不会让你去杀人
and I will not let you kill those people.
等等，等等，等
Wait, wait, wait.
什么，你准备回归以前的生活？
What, you're gonna live a regular life
和那个贱人Alice，在古玩店？
with that bitch, Alice, from the antique store?
她有个二B猫
She has a stupid cat,
她左边屁股上有个恶心的胎记
she has a disgusting birthmark on her left hip.
她做的菜我无力吐槽
She's a lousy fucking cook.
好吧，相信我
Okay, trust me.
她不能把持我们的秘密
She can't handle our secrets.
她不能，相信我。她和我们不是一路人
She can't, trust me. She's not right for us.
你不知道什么对我而言才是正确的
You have no idea what is right for me.
好，好，好，我们是好基友
Okay, okay, okay, all we have is each other.
这就是我们曾经拥有的
It is all we've ever had.
那，如果你朝我开枪
Now if you shoot me
你将变成我
you'll become me.
你的，明白？
You get it?
那就是它如何发生的
That's how it happens.
如果你想打破循环
If you want to break the chain
你就不能杀我
you have to not kill me
而是再次的爱我
but try to love me, again.
如果我把他放到你面前
What if I put him in front of you,
那个毁了你一生的男人...
the man who ruined your life...
别扯犊子了
Forget all that.
我们能够一起有个未来
We can have a future together.
你会杀了他
Would you kill him
去拯救千万生命？
to save thousands?
你想知道我们打算明天做什么？
You wanna know what we're gonna do tomorrow?
不
No.
给你
Here you are
在你新生命的开始
at the beginning of your new life.
它不可阻挡
It can be overwhelming
知道你将创建的未来
knowing the future you're about to create.
知道生命的意义
Knowing the purpose of that life.
你知道她是谁
You know who she is.
并且你明白你是谁
And you understand who you are.
现在，也许你准备好了解我是谁
And now maybe you're ready to understand who I am.
你看见我也爱她
You see I love her, too.
你将不得不做个艰难的决定
You'll have to make tough choices.
你将影响过去
You'll influence the past.
我们能重塑未来？
Can we change our futures?
我不知道
I don't know.
而我唯一肯定的是
The only thing that I know for sure
你就是我这辈子最美好的事情
is that you are the best thing that's ever happened to me.
我真的很想你
I miss you dreadfully.
北邮人 四月一日君制作（仅供交流，没了射手网，只能自个翻译）
学术交流、节操一地、介绍对象请 Email： 317919568@qq.com
前目的地/宿命论
欢迎关注新浪微博：侑子小姐的宠物店